

585 Purdue Mall ME3171, West Lafayette, IN 47907

🗷 hgchi@purdue.edu | 🏕 engineering.purdue.edu/people/hyung.gun.chi.1 | 🞧 stnoah1 | 🛅 hyung-gun | 🎓 Hyung-gun Chi

Research Interests

My research interests lie in the fields of Computer Vision and Machine Learning. More specifically, I am interested in the Representation Learning for human action, 3D Computer Vision, and their applications in VR / AR devices and Autonomous Vehicles.

Education

Purdue UniversityWest Lafayette, IN, USA

PHD IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Dec. 2023 (Expected)

Dec 2022

• Thesis: Learning Representation for Understanding Human Action

• Advisor: Prof. Karthik Ramani

Purdue University West Lafayette, IN, USA

MS IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Advisor: Prof. Karthik Ramani

Yonsei UniversitySeoul, South Korea

BS in Mechanical Engineering Feb. 2017

Publications and Patents

Conference Proceedings

- [C7] H. Chi, K. Lee, N. Agarwal, K. Ramani, and C. Choi. AdamsFormer for Spatial Action Localization in the Future, *Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)*, 2023. Submitted.
- [C6] H. Chi*, S. Chi*, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. Skeleton-ODE: Learning Representation by Predicting the Future for Online Skeleton-based Action Recognition, Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2023. Submitted.
- [C5] Y. Xu, A. Bazarjani, H. Chi, C. Choi, and Y. Fu. Uncovering the Missing Pattern: Unified Framework Towards Trajectory Imputation and Prediction, Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2023. Submitted.
- [C4] H. Chi*, S. Chi*, S. Chan, and K. Ramani. Pose Relation Transformer: Refine Occlusions for Human Pose Estimation, *IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA*), 2023. To appear.
- [C3] H. Chi*, M. Ha*, S. Chi, S. Lee, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. InfoGCN: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition, In proceedings of *Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)*, 2022.
- [C2] H. Chi*, S. Kim*, X. Hu, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. A Large-scale Mechanical Components Benchmark for Deep Neural Networks. In proceedings of the 16th European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2020.
- [C1] S. Kim, H. Chi, and K. Ramani. First-Person View Hand Segmentation of Multi-Modal Hand Activity Video Dataset. In proceedings of the 31st British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC), 2020.

Journal Papers

- [J3] S. Kim, H. Chi and K. Ramani. Object synthesis by learning part geometry with surface and volumetric representations. In Computer-Aided Design (2021): 102932.
- [J2] S. Kim, N. Winovich, H. Chi, G. Lin, and K. Ramani. Latent transformations neural network for object view synthesis. In *The Visual Computer* (2019): 1-15.
- [J1] H. T. Hwang, H. Chi, N. K. Kang, H. B. Kong and Soo-Hong Lee. An Evaluation Methodology for 3D Deep Neural Network using Visualization in 3D Data Classification. In *Journal of Mechanical Science and Technology (JMST)* 33, no. 3 (2019): 1333-1339.

Preprinted papers

• S. Kim, J. Bae, **H. Chi**, S. Hong, B.S. Koh, and K. Ramani. Egocentric View Hand Action Recognition by Leveraging Hand Surface and Hand Grasp Type. *arXiv preprint arXiv:2109.03783*, 2021.

Patents

- [P2] K. Ramani, S. Kim, and H. Chi. Pixel-wise Hand Segmentation of Multi-modal Hand Activity Video Dataset. U.S. Patent Application No. 17/109,193.
- [P1] H. Chi. Computer input system for office/factory automation. WO Patent No. 18/074729, issued 2018.

Work and Research Experience _____

Honda Research Institute

San Jose, CA, USA

Jan. 2023 - Apr. 2023

RESEARCH INTERN

- Host: Dr. Kwonjoon Lee
- Conducted human motion prediction research for autonomous vehicles.

Honda Research Institute

San Jose, CA, USA

Aug. 2018 - Present

Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2017

Jan. 2016 - Aug. 2016

RESEARCH INTERN

May. 2022 - Aug. 2022

· Host: Dr. Chiho Choi

• Conducted research on future action forcasting task for autonomous vehicles.

Purdue University West Lafayette, IN, USA

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

• Convergence Design Lab (Advisor: Prof. Karthik Ramani)

• Conducted skeleton-based human action recognition and pose estimation research.

NEIL LAB Corporation Seoul, South Korea

SOFTWARE ENGINEER & CEO

• Founded and managed a start-up company as a CEO.

• Developed an office automation system specifically for automating office works.

Yonsie University Seoul, South Korea

Undergraduate Researcher

• Knowledge-based Design Lab (Advisor: Prof. Soo-Hong Lee)

• Participated on the 3D computuer vision research.

Skills_

Research and Development Stacks Other Tools and Skills

Major Languages Python, C/C++ Text Editors Neovim & Vim

Machine LearningPyTorch, TensorFlow, KerasOther LangaugesShell Scripts(bszh, zsh), Matlab(Octave), RWeb FrameworksDjango, Flask, Node.jsOperating SystemsmacOS, Linux Debian/Ubuntu, Windows

Computer VisionOpenCV, OpenGLIDEVSCode, Eclipse, IDEA

Web Languages Nginx, React, HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS Softwares SolidWorks, Catia, AutoCAD

Database MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite, MongoDB **VCS Git**

Academic Activities

Reviewer

• The IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR) 2023

- · The IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV) 2023
- \cdot The British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC) 2020, 2021, 2022
- \cdot The IEEE Conference on Artificial Intelligence (CAI) 2023
- · Journal of Visual Communication and Image Representation (JVCI)
- · Journal of Computing and Information Science in Engineering (JCISE)

Invited Talks_

Hongik UniversitySeoul, South Korea

Guest Lecturer: Learning Representation for Human Action Recognition

Dec. 2022

Honors & Awards

KISTI (Korea Institute of Science and Technology Information) President's Award,

Seoul, South Korea

CDE (Korea Society for Computational Design and Engineering) President's Award,

2016 CDE (Korea Society for Computational Design and Engineering) President's Award,

Daejeon, South Korea

CDE Challenge – Computational Design and Engineering Tools Section

N. C.

References.

Karthik Ramani Professor, Purdue University ramani@purdue.edu **Soo-Hong Lee** Professor, Yonsei University shlee@yonsei.ac.kr

Edison Challenge – Computer Aided Design Section